// quiz questions
const STORE = [
    {
        question: "Who is the king of all gods (and father to many)?",
        choices: [
            "Aphrodite",
            "Ares",
            "Poseidon",
            "Zeus",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Zeus"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the goddess of beauty and love?",
        choices: [
            "Aphrodite",
            "Demeter",
            "Minerva",
            "Hermes",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Aphrodite"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the goddess of hunting, animals, and childbirth?",
        choices: [
            "Aphrodite",
            "Athena",
            "Apolla",
            "Artemis",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Artemis"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the god of wine, pleasure, and festivity?",
        choices: [
            "Ares",
            "Hermes",
            "Poseidon",
            "Dionysos",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Dionysos"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the god of war?",
        choices: [
            "Hephaistos",
            "Ares",
            "Poseidon",
            "Zeus",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Ares"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the god of the Sea? ",
        choices: [
            "Hermes",
            "Hera",
            "Poseidon",
            "Hades",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Poseidon"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the god of fire, metalworking, and sculpture?",
        choices: [
            "Hades",
            "Demeter",
            "Hephaistos",
            "Hermes",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Hephaistos"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the goddess of wisdom and defense?",
        choices: [
            "Aphrodite",
            "Athena",
            "Hestia",
            "Eros",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Athena"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the god of travel, hospitality and trade (also Zeus's personal messenger)?",
        choices: [
            "Apollo",
            "Ares",
            "Poseidon",
            "Hermes",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Hermes"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the god of prophecy, music and poetry and knowledge?",
        choices: [
            "Apollo",
            "Hermes",
            "Hestia",
            "Eros",
        ],
        correctAnswer: "Apollo"
    }
];

